(Tsujimoto) These are the people Kosaka-san was in charge of.
All nine people here have disappeared from prison.
The plan is to rewrite criminals' memories and reintegrate them into society.
(Igawa) Let's take back my daughter... and your life too.
7 years? separated from my daughter
I haven't been able to see my daughter for a while due to something happening.
(Tsumura) What do you plan to do with Nanami Ishino?
She didn't kill her husband, she did...
Isn't it Muroya?
I thought this project had a future.
Even pretending that Ninomiya was dead
Why did you choose to be reborn as Masaki Igawa?
What did Ninomiya do?
Everything
♬〜
Yuri
(Yuri) Yusuke?
I'm home
What about Tsumura-san?
He was... caught.
After all, he was killing people.
Ninomiya!
≪Everything back to normal...≫
(Sage) I'm going
Take care
Be careful
Yeah!
I feel like... it still feels like a lie?
I thought I was alone with Kento for a long time.
sorry…
What happened? You remember everything, right?
I learned about the project and opposed it.
(Sigh) So my memory was erased.
Huh? That's... that's too bad.
Apparently it was started by some people going out of control.
The project is now abolished
Hehe... it's okay now
Really? Yeah
Are you going back to the police?
No, I'll look for another job.
A job that allows me to spend some time with Yuri and Kento.
Hehe... yeah
What about Mayumi? Huh?
What happened?
Hehe... it's okay
You started living in a safe place with your child.
good
♬〜
Okay, I'll do it.
I'm just doing it because I want to do it
Did you remember?
As soon as someone I worked with before got married,
She was complaining that her husband had suddenly become overbearing.
I think Yusuke is the opposite.
After getting married, I became more kind.
Hehe... Huh? Is that so?
That's right, because last time I ate some rice or something.
The dishes were left on the table.
Take off your socks too.
When Pepe took off her clothes, she kept taking them off.
No, no, that's not the case.
Yeah? Sorry yes hehehehe
But I'm a sage thanks to my dad
He will help you with everything
I see.
♬〜
Shall we go to the sea park next holiday?
Huh? The wise man is happy
Hehehe
(cell phone vibration sound)
I'll be late for work... Yeah.
I'm going. What about Yusuke?
I think I'll take it easy today. It's been a while since I've been home.
Please come back in the evening.
I'm going
♬〜
(Sound of door opening and closing)
≪When will it start? ≫
♬〜
≪Lying became okay≫
I'm glad you're back
Even if short-term memories can be erased
Because only you can rewrite your memories
(Kousaka) 2 years ago Why did you rewrite your memories?
Why did you lie to Yuri that you were a police officer?
≪When did I... make a mistake?≫
♬〜
(Soma) 《Is this...sure? 》
《Yes, the memory of the mouse that memorized the route of the maze.
convert it into an electrical signal
We succeeded in writing to the brain of another mouse》
《Theoretically, even more complex memories can be transplanted.》
《Can it be applied to the human brain? 》
《I think it is possible》
《Sigh... This is an incredible invention that will change history.》
《Please proceed, I will give you any amount of research funds》
《Thank you》 (Soma)《Hahahaha》
≪This could help many people suffering from PTSD.
I seriously thought so≫
(Soma)《He suffered severe brain damage in the accident.
It seems that he is suffering from memory impairment.
(Soma)《He wants those of us who are suffering to be cured》
(Soma)《I can't say I'm lucky, but it seems like I don't have any family.》
《He says he wants to be reborn as a different person》
《I don't think there is any problem with transplanting memories from a donor.
There is still sufficient verification...》
(Soma)《He is...》
《He says he doesn't mind if they use him as an experiment》
《Huh...》
(Soma)《Even if I experiment with mice forever
Research is not progressing.
《This is a big step towards perfecting this technology.》
♬〜
(Tablet Tada) "Please tell me your name"
《``Tachibana... I'm Naoya.''》
《“This is...”》
"I'm at the hospital. I've been in an accident."
``I may not have any recollection of that time, but
It's okay because it wasn't anything serious."
(Soma)《Hehehehe…》
《Next test subject, please proceed》
"got it"
♬〜
《Welcome back》
"I'm home"
♬〜
"yeah? 》
"what happened? 》
《I feel happy》
《Hehe what? that"
《I'll warm up the rice.》 《Yeah, are you okay? 》
"Yeah"
♬〜
≪I can't go back anymore≫
≪If this happiness continues forever
That's fine≫
≪I had come to wish so≫
《What does this mean? 》
“They are not patients with brain damage.”
《They are all criminals》
《That's not all》
《This man named Murotani is the first test subject, right? 》
``What happened? 》 《(Knock)》
(Uemoto)《Excuse me》
(Soma) 《I'd like to introduce it to you》
《This is Mr. Uemoto and Mr. Kosaka from the Metropolitan Police Department》
(Soma)《This is Ninomiya》《Kimi?》
《Thank you for your wonderful invention》
《I'm going down》
《This technology helps people who suffer from past trauma.
It's for saving.
《Excuse me》
《Do you think you can get away with it now that you know? 》
《What happened to you, Tsumura, was unfortunate.》
《You know each other, right? 》
《Please be at ease》
《Nothing about this project has been disclosed to the public.》
《You will not suffer any damage from now on》
"what do you mean? 》
"As long as you're on this side, you're safe."
"Family is important"
"(cry)"
(Soma)《It no longer depends on your will.》
≪Why...≫
≪This is what happened...≫
♬〜
≪Where did I go wrong? ≫
《There is an abnormality in the brain waves...》
《I'll take a look》
♬〜
``What is he doing? 》
《“Hey Ninomiya, what are you kidding?”》
《I don't want to get my hands dirty anymore》
⚞(Tada)《Open it! 》
♬〜
(Tada)《Oi Ninomiya
Stop being stupid, Ninomiya, hey.”
《“What are you doing?”》
(Tada)《“Hey Ninomiya!”》
♬〜
≪If I stop being me
There is no danger to Yuri or Kento.
《This is fine》
《Now...》
♬〜
《What should we do...》
《Yusuke Ninomiya is assumed to be dead》
《I will tell my wife》
"got it"
《For now, we will keep you under our supervision》
《I'll try to see if my memory returns》
After I became Igawa
Has that project been stopped?
(Kousaka) Yeah, but these past seven years.
There is not a single case where memory returned except for Nanami Ishino.
Is the cause psychological shock?
perhaps
you too?
《Remember...》
《Come back, Yusuke》
♬〜
Please do not approach Yuri or Kento.
Keep your promises
After Nanami Ishino and Tsumura's treatment was completed
What will happen to those two?
be on one's mind?
Arrange to live as a different person in another place
Is that okay?
yes
But instead...
I also have one thing I would like to ask.
(unlock sound)
8 years ago, at the scene of an indiscriminate murder committed by Muroya...
There was also a daughter
♬〜
I was on my way home from cram school.
(Hina)《Kya! 》
(Murotani)《Urusaeena》
(Male)《Hey, the criminal turned around》
♬〜
(Detective)《Once we arrive, we will check the damage situation》 (Detective)《Yes! 》
《(Vibration sound of mobile phone)》
"what happened? 》
📱《(Yuzuki's cry)》
《Yuzu season? 》 📱《(Yuzuki's cry)》
《Where are you? 》 📱《(Yuzuki's cry)》
《Tsujimoto hold it! " "yes! 》
(Murotani)《Hahahahahahaha, it's your fault that I failed to kill him.
There must be someone suffering.
《I'll make things easier for you right now, so let go of me》
《Ah...》 (Tsujimoto)《Mr. Tsumura! 》
《What is the condition? 》 《There is breath》
♬〜
《Yuzu season Yuzu season! 》
《Ah...》
(Tsujimoto)《Mr. Tsumura! 》 《Let go! 》
《Yuzu season...Yuzu season...》
《Yuzu season...Yuzu season! 》
《Yuzu season! 》
《Yuzu season? 》
《Yuzu season! 》 《(Yuzuki's cry)》
《It's okay, it's okay now》
《I'm sorry... I'm sorry...》
《(Yuzuki's cry)》
(Kousaka) I'm glad you ran away.
I'm glad it wasn't Yuzuki who was the victim.
(Kousaka) That's what I thought.
(Kousaka) But... Yuzuki was also a victim.
Since then, I've closed my heart and stopped showing myself.
I lost my smile
♬〜
Rewrite Yuzuki's memory
save that kid
Is that why you participated in that project?
Yeah
(Kousaka) Because of that...
It also ruined your friend Tsumura's life.
If you want to despise it, go ahead.
But please help me with this
I won't disrespect you
I understand your desire to protect your loved ones.
2 years ago you erased your memory
Was it to protect his family?
♬〜
Actually... maybe I should have died.
(Researcher) Huh?
What are you doing!
Hey, call the medical team! yes!
(Researcher) Maybe...
♬〜
Ah...
(alarm sound)
I make sure you proceed with the work
yes
(alarm sound)
(unlock sound)
Are you okay? Eh, wait... what's going on?
Let's go
(alarm sound)
♬〜
☎(Researcher) “Tsumura ran away!”
(Kousaka)Yuzuki
(Kousaka) Yuzuki It's okay, this is a hospital.
(breathing heavily) Yuzuki!
Let go!
calm down! Yuzuki
no! Yuzu season!
This is not a hospital
Erase the memory of that incident from you
Wait, what are you saying? There's no way I can do that.
I don't have to remember anymore
No... Absolutely no...
(breathing heavily) Yuzuki...
Because I... ran away alone...
Because I... abandoned you...
No, no difference!
I killed...
So...don't forget! Forget it!
I forget in order to live
There are people who want you to smile
For that person...
To smile in front of your loved ones
you can smile
♬〜
(Tada) Hey, it's nice weather.
I hope the weather is nice...
It makes me feel better, doesn't it?
♬〜
(sigh)
Ninomiya was a Neurovis person.
I tricked you
What do you do now?
I'm going to pick up Miu.
Neurovise?
If you don't do well, the police might be involved.
(sound of breathing)
Sorry
Huh? ruined your life
It's not you
I'm speaking on behalf of the police.
you are not a police officer
surely
But thank you
I'll do something
Could you please wait here for a while?
(typing sound)
Data will be completed soon
Anytime after checking for bugs
When will it end? At dawn tomorrow
Okay, please come here at 7 o'clock, I understand.
♬〜
Huh, isn't there a lot? That (sage) is okay.
TRUE? I'm home
Welcome back!
Welcome back
Where have you been?
I thought I had to find a job after all.
I was hired by a security company I know.
That's right
Gyoza today?
Tell daddy how to make it too (Kento) Okay.
How are you doing? (Sage) Yes
this? (Sage) Yeah
♬〜
≪Do whatever≫
≪If you can see this smile...≫
≪Anything≫
♬〜
good morning
(Sage) What about daddy?
I have to work from today.
That's right.
Come on, go wash your face.
Well then, 2 plus 3
(Sage) 2 plus 3 is... 5?
5 Correct
Then 4 plus 2
4 plus 2 is... 6 Correct
Well then, please be careful when you go.
Yes yes yes
Take care
♬〜
Kya!
Stop it! What about Ninomiya?
Are you at home? To work...
It's better to stay away from him
♬〜
Somewhere with Kento-kun for a while...
(cell phone vibration sound)
Really... please
start
♬〜
It's okay now
(cell phone vibration sound)
Excuse me for a moment
Hello 📱 “Kento…”
what up?
I received a call from a person named Muroya...
He said he kidnapped a wise man.
Muroya…
📱"If you want it back, you two should come together."
Why is Kento... Why...
My son was kidnapped by Muroya.
Was Muroya alive?
♬〜
(noise)
Sage!
who? Papa...
What about women? Oh, did you ask me?
(Muroya) Don't move.
That child has nothing to do with it!
(Muroya) Yes, that woman's child, right?
Even if I die, the wound he gave me won't go away.
Sage! Ah...
Sage!
Muroya you...
Mom!
(Muroya) Don't delay! Let go of Kento, both of you!
Okay
♬〜
Let's go! It's a touching reunion.
Kya!
Sage!
♬〜
Hey, that face of yours...
It's the best
♬〜
ambulance!
Sage!
♬〜
"mother! 》
"why! 》
♬〜
Yuri?
(breathing heavily)
Good luck, Kento!
(Doctor) Go away!
♬〜
Is Kento okay?
The bleeding is severe and a blood transfusion is required.
Kento has a rare blood type of B Rh-negative.
Blood products are currently being transported from the blood center.
Will you make it in time?
please use my blood
I am also B Rh negative.
I appreciate your offer.
For safety reasons, blood transfusions will be performed using blood products.
Click here to sign the consent form
Please help the sage please
♬〜
It's okay now
See you later
good…
Ah... ah...
(sob)
♬〜
I have something I want to ask you
Why did that person kidnap the wise man?
What happened with that person?
Tell me, Yusuke
It's my fault
Because of me, you and Kento were targeted.
Huh? What do you mean?
it is…
7 years ago we...
were supposed to get married
♬〜